Hello friends, my name is Ashwini Kumar.
As you all must be knowing here,
brother friends, I
work here in II Bank. Friends,
here I am a customer executive. Friends, today's
video is going to be here.
You must have seen it in the title and thumbnail. The
topic of today's video is going to be, brother, if you
want to do a job at the entry level, you
want to go here in a private sector
bank. So friends, your CASA
profile can be
entry level here. If friends, you
want to work in the banking sector. CASA profile friends, here
comes in sales. If you go to CASA,
once you enter, you
go to CASA and get one to two
years of experience here. So, brother
friends, your growth here is going to be
very good. Friends,
how much salary do you get in this? How much target are you given in this?
How much pressure do you have here? Is this an
honorary job or do you have to work
in the feed?  You have to be 100% focused on
how much sales you have to make, what is the
timing for it, brother, what is that timing, brother, when you
sit in the bank, like you go
to any bank,
you see that there are a lot of
people sitting here, among them, there is
also a person from Casa,
if you are searching for a job in Casa profile,
and
brother, you want to go to Casa profile, then
friends, you should
definitely watch this video till the end because brother,
you have some doubts here, they will be cleared here,
friends, in today's video, I am going to
tell you
how you can go to Casa profile, and brother, what
work is going to be there,
how much is your salary going to be, what
work will you have to do here,
friends, before leaving, let me give
you one more update, we have a lot of
vacancies coming up here, and brother, some
vacancies are currently open, some hiring is going on with us right now.  If
you are interested in hdfcfund.com up to 00 0000, brother,
you will get the same content here for ₹
and brother friends, we will
also get your placement done here free of cost.
We are going to talk about Casa profile,
so brother, you will get complete information about it in today's
video,
for this, friends, you have to do only one thing, if you like the
video then give it a like,
if brother, you are new to this channel, then
friends, you must subscribe to the channel here
because friends,
you keep getting helpful content here, let's
start the video without wasting time,
friends, we are talking about Casa
profile here, friends, let
me tell you the full form of Casa,
Current Account and Savings, brother,
here the major source of the bank in the banking sector,
brother, here
Casa remains the focus here because brother,
what happens is that the bank which earns money here, it also
earns from Casa here,
as its current account saving
account increases here  If more than this amount is opened, then
brother, similarly, friends, there will be a benefit of the bank here,
so brother, this
person is hired here,
what does he do specifically for Casa, he
looks after the current account here and brother, he gets the
savings account opened here, but
he is given some tasks here for the day,
friends, those who are in the Casa profile, they have some targets here,
brother, they have to hit them, but they are
given targets for the day, but they are also given targets for the month,
their team leader, who is the
branch manager, he
takes reports from them here, he takes
reports in the evening, he takes reports in the morning,
whatever report they have, he
takes them here, brother, how many accounts do you have to
open, how many accounts have you opened,
what is your status,
friends, he will take complete information from you, what you have to do in the first time,
you have to
take entry by 9:30 in the morning, after taking the entry,
friends, there are meetings etc. with you, there are
heads etc. which are held
in every bank, whether you are
in the Casa profile or in any other bank
Your handle in the profile has to be 100%, the
handle is from 9:00 am to 10:00 am,
you have to join here, in that
you are told how
you have to work, how you should
not work, what
strategies you have to follow so that
you can open a current account, savings account, at the
most, so brother, all these things are
told to you, you have a normal meeting
here, then after that, in the afternoon, brother,
if you want to go to the feed, then brother,
you can go to the feed, if brother, brother, you want to
sit there, then you can sit there,
it will depend on you, brother,
how you do it, brother, here
in the Casa profile, you grow your business here, let's
talk about the
salary here, brother, the salary here is going to be from
₹1 to
friends, your salary here can be up to ₹0000, it is an
entry level job, brother, if brother, you gain a
good amount of experience here, then
brother  Later on, friends, you
become an ADM, an ARM, and after doing a BDM, you get
posted here. In that,
you become a BRM here. As
your experience increases,
your package also increases. For example, if
you gain two to three years of experience in a CASA profile here, if
you work in another bank,
your package can range from ₹100,000 to ₹100,000.
If you have a good amount of
experience here, the
CASA profile is an entry-level job. If you want to get into the banking sector, then the CASA profile here is your entry-
level job.
If you have the courage and
can work hard, then this profile could be the
best for you. Because, in
this profile, you will have to work hard.
You will have to run around. 100%
okay, your hard work and brother, in this.  You are
also given incentives etc. In this
you are given incentives up to ₹ Hajj, rest
brother there are some great people who
complete this incentive here
and brother there are some people who are
not even able to do it, rest friends you
see if you want to work hard, if you can
work hard then brother
you should come to this profile, in the Casa profile,
friends its hiring is going to come to us,
after some time friends
hiring for the Casa profile will come to us as well,
till then friends you wait here on WhatsApp your
age should be plus 2 years,
second friends you should have
completed graduation with plus marks out of 50,
friends this
is its criteria here, rest brother you should have a
bike, you should have a license,
if brother you want to go to the Casa profile,
then rest friends here the
work is done in this way,
brother you are given a target per day, you are
also given a target per day, you are
also given a target per month
You have to complete that target,
if you are not able to do it, then
you may have to listen to it, it will depend on your
branch manager, whoever is your team
leader, brother, how much he
tells you and how much he does not
tell you, rest friends, here you can have a profile by doing a Casa
profile, savings account, current account, there is
a good
entry level job here, if
you also want to do it, then you
can do it here, rest friends, here I have
told you complete information about it, I
hope you liked this video very much, if you liked the
video then give it a like,
if you have not subscribed to this channel yet, then
go quickly and subscribe to this channel, see you
in the next video, take care
bye